<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Hello &lt;TechEd&gt; World!</title>
    <link href="https://AneteZepa.github.io/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://AneteZepa.github.io/blog" />
    <updated>2025-09-16T16:39:53+03:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Anete Zepa</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://AneteZepa.github.io/blog</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Hello &lt;TechEd&gt; World! - Intro</title>
        <author>
            <name>Anete Zepa</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://AneteZepa.github.io/blog/hello-lesstechedgreater-world-intro/"/>
        <id>https://AneteZepa.github.io/blog/hello-lesstechedgreater-world-intro/</id>
        <media:content url="https://AneteZepa.github.io/blog/media/posts/1/IMG_1951.JPG" medium="image" />

        <updated>2025-09-16T16:31:30+03:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://AneteZepa.github.io/blog/media/posts/1/IMG_1951.JPG" alt="Anete Zepa on a red brakgorund" />
                    This space is dedicated to practical ideas, tools, and methods that improve technical (topic) learning and education. Whether you’re a beginner, educator, team lead, or simply a tech enthusiast, I hope you’ll find posts here that help you teach, learn, or think more clearly. I’ve&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://AneteZepa.github.io/blog/media/posts/1/IMG_1951.JPG" class="type:primaryImage" alt="Anete Zepa on a red brakgorund" /></p>
                
  <p>
    This space is dedicated to practical ideas, tools, and methods that improve technical (topic) learning and education.
  </p>

  <p>
    Whether you’re a <em>beginner, educator, team lead</em>, or simply a <em>tech enthusiast</em>, I hope you’ll find posts here that help you teach, learn, or think more clearly.
  </p>

    <h2 id="a-bit-about-me-waveandnbsp">
      A bit about me :wave:&nbsp;
    </h2>

  <p>
    I’ve been working in tech education for over five years, starting while studying 'MComp AI and Computer Science' at the University of Sheffield.<br><br>Since then, I’ve worked across the tech education space as a learning experience designer, instructor, and content creator. Frequently, all at the same time.
  </p>

  <p>
    I’ve built bite-sized lessons for mobile learning apps (<a href="https://www.sololearn.com/en/" target="_blank">Sololearn</a>), UK apprenticeship programs (<a href="https://www.multiverse.io/en-GB" target="_blank">Multiverse</a>, <a href="https://www.manchesterdigital.com/" target="_blank">Manchester Digital</a>, <a href="https://flipcomputing.com/" target="_blank">Flip Computing</a>), internal company training,&nbsp;MOOCs, and live classes (<a href="https://codefirstgirls.com/" target="_blank">Code First Girls</a>), and more.
  </p>

  <p>
    I’ve worked with learners at many levels, from <strong>complete beginners to aspiring leaders,</strong> across topics like coding, AI, web development, leadership, and data.<br>
  </p>

    <h2 id="what-will-this-blog-have">
      What will this blog have?
    </h2>

  <p>
    Good question! So far, I have come up with these guiding points:
  </p>

  <ul>
    <li>Insights into tech learning design and course creation - to AI or not to AI</li><li>Tips and frameworks for content creators and educators</li><li>Big-picture thoughts on education, tech culture, and how we grow<br></li><li>Educational takes on new tools, languages, and ideas</li>
  </ul>

  <p>
    Sometimes it’ll be a short post about a tool I loved this week. Other times, it might be advice for teaching difficult topics or how we can build better developer education programs. Either way, it’ll be useful, honest, and aimed at making tech learning a little better for everyone.
  </p>

    <h2 id="phylosophy">
      Phylosophy
    </h2>

  <p>
    I care most about the learner — because in a world of lifelong learning, we’re all learners. What if learning felt natural, personal, and just right? That’s the kind of future I want to help build.
  </p>

  <ul>
    <li>Education is for everyone, and it should be built like that</li><li>AI will make education better</li><li>You cannot learn how to code without coding</li><li>Sometimes it was your teacher’s fault</li>
  </ul>

  <p>
    Thanks for stopping by.<br>— Anete
  </p>

  <p>
    TLDR: Welcome to "Hello &lt;TechEd&gt; World!"—a blog focused on effective tech education. The author, with over five years of experience in tech education, will share insights on tools, learning design, and content creation.
  </p>

  <p>
    
  </p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
